Hope is uncharted territory.
Greenland 2: Migration is a action, adventure,
thriller film directed by Ric Roman Waugh.
Having found the safety of the Greenland bunker after the comet Clarke decimated the Earth, the Garrity family must
now risk everything to embark on a perilous journey across the wasteland of Europe to find a new home.
John Garrity, played by Gerard Butler.
Allison Garrity, played by Morena Baccarin.
General Sharpe, played by Tommie Earl Jenkins.
Adam Shaw, played by Trond Fausa Aurvåg.
Dr Casey Amina, played by Amber Rose Revah.
Elizabeth Price, played by Gina Gangar.
Greenland 2: Migration is a 2026 American post-apocalyptic survival disaster thriller film
directed by Ric Roman Waugh and written by Chris Sparling and Mitchell LaFortune.
The sequel to Greenland (2020), the film stars Gerard Butler and Morena Baccarin reprising their roles, alongside Roman Griffin Davis (who
replaces Roger Dale Floyd), Amber Rose Revah, Gordon Alexander, Peter Polycarpou, William Abadie, and Tommie Earl Jenkins.
The film was first released in Austria on January 6, 2026, and then in
the United States on January 9, 2026, by Lionsgate.
It received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of natural disaster, shelter, survival, disaster.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.